αερον εφορίας των καρπόδης γης και χαιρών ειρηνικών του Κυρίου Δεηθώμεν, Κύριε λέει σώμαν,
ερπλέον των οδιπορούν των οσούν των καννώ των εκμαλώτων και της σωτηρίας αυτών του Κυρίου Δεηθώμεν, Κύριε λέει σώμαν,
Υπέρ του ρίστην αίη μας από πάσης,
σλήψει ως οργής, κινδύνο και ανάγκης του Κύριου Δεηθώμες.
Κύριε λέει σώμα.
Αντιλάβους όσων ελέησον και διαφύλαξουν ημάς ο Θεός της η χάρητη.
Κύριε ελέησον.
Σπαραγία σαχράν του υπερευλογημένης εν τόξου δεσπινήσιμον Θεό τούχο και υπαρθένου Μαρίας.
Με τα πάντων άγιων ημονεύσαντες εαυτούς και αλληλούς και πάσαν την ζωήν ημών Χριστό το Θεό παραθώμεθα.
Συ Κύριε.
Ότι πρέπει σοι πάσα δόξα τιμή και προσκύνει.
Στο πατρί και το Υιό και το Άγιο Πνεύμα την δίν και αϊκέ εις τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Αμήν Θεός Κύριος και επεφανένημιν ευλογημένος ο ερχόμενος εν ονόματι Κυρίου.
Εξομολογήστε το Κύριο και επικαλήστε το όνομα το Άγιον Αυτού.
Θεός Κύριος και Επεφανένη, μείν ευλογημένος ο ελληνός.
Αντιλαβούς όσων ελέησον κι διαφύλαξον ημάς ο Θεός της ηχάρητης
της Παναγίας Αχράντου υπερευλογημένης εντόξου δεσποινήσιμων Θεοτόκου και υπαρεθένου Μαρίας
με τα πάντων των Αγίων μνημονεύσανται σε αυτούς και αλλήλους και πάσαν την ζωήν ημών
Χριστό το Θεό παραθώ
Αμήν.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
From my youth many passions,
Κούντες Ιόνες κύνθητε από του Κυρίου
ως χόρτος γαρπύρι.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
εξηραμένη
Τι κινόβωτε και καθαρσιν τζούτελα πρινέτε
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Κύριε Αλάησον, Κύριε Αλάησον, Κύριε Αλάησον, Κύριε Αλάησον, Κύριε Αλάησον, Κύριε Αλάησον, Κύριε Αλάησον.
ΑΛΕΙΚΙΚΤΗΡΜΗΣ ΚΕΦΗΛΑΤΡΟΠΗΑ ΤΟΥ ΜΟΝΟΓΕΝΟΥ ΣΟΙΟΥ ΕΒΛΟΓΗ ΤΟΣΗΣ
ΕΣΥΝ ΤΟΟΥ ΠΑΝΑΓΙΟ ΚΕΓΑΘΟ ΚΕΣΟΠΗΣΟΥ ΠΝΕΒΝΑΝΟΥ
Amen.
The barren one bears the Theotokos, the nourisher of our lives.
The prayer with the sigh sterile and barren of Joachim and of Anna was well received in the ears of the Lord.
It unbound them and they blossomed the fruit that brings life to the world.
For while he on the mountain did offer a prayer, she in the garden the reproach did bear.
but then with joy the barren one bears the Theodokos.
η πηγή της ζωής εκ της τυραστικτέται, η χάρης καρπογόνην λαμπρός απαρχεται.
Εφραίνου Ιωάκημ της Θεοτόπου γεννήτορ γεννόμενος,
ουκέ στην άλο ζωσή των γηγενών γεννητόρων θεόληπτε.
Praise Him with the sound of trumpet, praise Him with the harp and lyre.
What a paradoxical miracle that the fountain of life from above.
And wife is born, that graceful gent may commence to bear its fruit and sport.
Be joyous, O Joachim, having become the God-bearer's progenitor.
There is no one else like you in generations of paternity, O godly one.
for the God-receiving maiden.
Ευλογημένη βασιλεία του Πατρός και του Υιού και του Αγιού Πνεύματος, νυν και αϊκέης τους αιώνας των αιώνων,
εν ειρήνη του Κυρίου Δεηθώμεν, υπέρ της ανώθεν ειρήνης και της σωτηριάς των ψυχών ημών του Κυρίου Δεηθώμεν,
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Υπέρ της ειρηνής του σήμαντος κόσμα εφταθίας των Αγίων του Θεού εκκλησιών και της των πάντων ενός αιώσ του Κυρίου δε ηθόμεν.
Υπέρ του Αγίου οίκου τούτου και των μεταπίστως ευλαβίας και φόβου Θεού ισιόντων εν αυτό του Κυρίου δε ηθόμεν.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Υπέρ του Αρχιεπισκόπου και πατρός Συμμον Νικολάου του Τιμίου Πρεσβυτερίου της εν Χριστώ διακονίας παντός του κλήρου και του λαού του Κυρίου Δεηθώμεν.
Κύριε, εκπέλεης ο, υπέρ του ευσεύγους, σύμων έθνους, πάσης αρχής και εξουσίας εν αυτόν του Κυρίου δε ηθόμεν.
εαυτούς και αλληλούς και πάσαν την ζωή νημών Χριστώ το Θεό παραθώμεθα
οτι σώτο κράτος και σου εστίν η βασιλεία και η δύναμις και η δόξα του Πατρός και του Υιού και του Αγίου Πνεύματος
νυν και αηκέις τους αιώνας των αιώνων
Αμήν, όμως ο Κύριος το Δάβιδ αλήθεια και ούστη αλήθεια
I shall set upon your throne, one from the fruit of your loins.
Save us, O Son of God, who are wondrous in the saints.
We sing to you, Alleluia.
There is a place where the Lord is coming from.
The Lord has chosen Zion.
He has chosen her for his dwelling.
Save us, O Son of God, who are wondrous in the saints.
We sing to you Alleluia.
for you are a good and loving God
and to you we give up glory
into the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit
now and forever and to the ages of ages
Amen
Here I shall dwell
for I am chosen
Your not in the field
I feel that all of us important.
Χαραπησήπασαι δόξα τέμει και παρσοπής, τον Πατρέ και τον Άγχναμο, νύν και αγιές της αιώνας, το λιώναν, ταμήν.
Εγώ ημένα, Άσαι, δόξα τέμει, ο πάντοτε είναι η χέρα της αιώνας του μόνος.
Αλλα, αλλα, αλλα.
As they cry out to you.
The bearing one bears the Theotokos.
The nourisher of our life.
To Kyrieu Dei Thomen.
O Diagio, Sio Theos, Simon,
K'Essi, Thin Doxan, αναpempo men.
and the Holy Spirit.
και το Υιό και το Άγιο Πνεύμα την Είν και Αΐ
και εις τους αιώνας των αιώνων
Amém.
Let us be attentive.
My soul magnifies the Lord
and my spirit rejoices in God my Savior
for he has regarded the humility of his service.
Wisdom.
The reading is for you.
From St. Paul's letter to the Philippians, let us be attentive.
Brethren, have this mind among yourselves, which is yours in Jesus Christ,
who though he was in the form of God, did not count equality with God a thing to be grasped,
but emptied himself, taking the form of a servant, being born in the likeness of men,
and being found in human form
he humbles
himself and became obedient unto death, even death on a cross. Therefore God has
highly exalted him and bestowed on him the name which is above every name, that
at the name of Jesus every knee should bow in heaven and on earth
and under the earth, and every tongue confess that Jesus Christ is Lord.
to the glory of God the Father.
Όπως υπό το κράτο σου πάντοτε φιλαθόμενης η δόξανα αναπέμπομεν
το πατρί και το αιών και το άγιο πνεύμα την δίν και αϊκέ εις τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Κατάφτερ πες και βγεις το άγγελ και αγαπημένους σου, μόκου χωμνό.
Σίγχαρ προς έρχομαι κλίνας τα συνοχτάκια.
Λυμήσω με αποστρέψου το πρόσωπό σου, άπε μου.
Μη δε αποδοχημάσαι με εκπαίδον σου, αλλά ξέσου αν προσευχήν εσύ παιδιά το μάτλο και τον αξίδον σου.
Δωρα τα αυτά σίγχαρ ιοπροσφερόμενος και προσδεχόμενος και διαδιδόμενος, χρήσι ο Θεός είμον.
και σύνδεω ξανά, πιάνε, σύντανα όπως η Πατρική Δευαλία και οι οποίες πιάνε,
για εγγυσμό στον έμορφε, για να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να γίνει και να
with all the saints that has commend ourselves and one another and our whole life to Christ our God.
.
νυν και αϊκέει στους αιώνας των αιώνων,
αγμύν, ειρήνη φάση,
με το Πνεύμα ειδήσου,
αγαπήσωμεν αλληλούσινα εν ομονία,
ομολογήσω με
Αγαπή σας ο Κύριος Γύριος μου και ο ίσκος μου
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Likewise, after supper, he took the cup, saying,
Drink of it, all of you, this is my blood of the new covenant,
shed for you and for many for the forgiveness of sins.
Remembering therefore the saving command of the Savior
All that came to pass for our sake the cross
the tomb, the resurrection, the third day, the center of heaven.
Enthroman at the right hand of the Father, the second glorious coming.
Amen.
Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done, on earth as it is in heaven.
give us this day our daily bread and forgive us our trespasses as we forgive those who
trespass against us, and lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from you. For thine is the kingdom, the power,
and the glory of the Father, and the Son, and the Holy Spirit,
now and forever, and in the ages of
ages. Amen.
Peace be with
all. And with your
Let us bow our heads.
to the Lord.
Those who sail, travel with those who travel
and heal the sick physician of our souls and bodies.
By the grace, mercy, and love for us
of your only begotten Son with whom you are blessed,
together with your all-holy, good, and life-giving Spirit,
now and forever and to the ages of ages.
Amen.
your inheritance.
We have seen the true
life. We have received
the heavenly spirit.
We have the true
faith. Worshiping
the undivided Trinity.
For the
Trinity
has
come.
Amen.
Αμήν.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
incarnation, and then to his crucifixion, to his resurrection, and to his ascension.
Those events really start in some way today with the birth of the Theotokos.
She is born.
In order for Christ to be born, the Theotokos must be born.
So this is the beginning of that series of events that leads to, ultimately, the salvation
of the whole world.
That's what happened.
happens today. So let's never forget
September 8th is not
just a random day in the
year. It's the beginning of
the chronicle in some ways
of salvation. So God bless you.
Thank you for being here today
in church. Please come forward for
Antidoro.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE